(Waiter:)...maybe I get bumped,
one of the dumplings fall to the floor.
No one has to know.
(Sheldon:)I'll know.
[SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
- How about soup?
- Yeah, we can always divide soup.
What about the won tons?
(Penny(answering):)Oh. Hey, guys, what's up?
It's "Halo" night.
Yeah? Okay.
(Leonard:)So?
(Leonard:)With Wolowitz spending all of his time
with your friend Christy...
(Penny:)She's not my friend. Friends do not
get their friends' Care Bears all sweaty.
(Leonard:)Right, anyway, uh,
with Wolowitz occupied elsewhere...
(Leonard:)...we had something
we wanted to ask you.
(Leonard:)- Sheldon?
- Yes. Ahem.
(Leonard(opening door):)Penny,
we would very much appreciate it...
(Sheldon:)...if you would be the fourth member
of our "Halo" team.
(Sheldon:)I don't think I need to tell you
what an honor this is.